thesnugg.com 2012-12-01

# Privacy Policy - TheSnugg.com USA

##  Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement explains how we collect, store and use the information you provide. 

Please read this privacy statement carefully, as once you use the TheSnugg.com website you will be deemed to have read and accepted this statement. 

##  What personal information is collected via the web site?

We will only collect personal information about you, given by you, when you complete a contact form requesting us to contact you or an application form. Please note that for your protection, telephone calls to our offices may be recorded and monitored. 

##  Cookies

When using this web site, some information may be collected automatically using ‘cookies'. These are small text files which facilitates the processing of your data and enables us to analyse how the site is being used. Two types of cookies are used: 

Temporary cookies - which form part of the security process while you are using the web site; and  
Permanent cookies - which identify the link you used to find our web site, check your browser so that we can make sure that our web site and services work well with your computer and to help us monitor traffic on our web site. 

We do not pass on, or sell cookies to any other companies. Further information on the use of cookies can be found at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

##  What happens to the information provided/collected?

We would like to pass your details on to other carefully selected companies so that they can provide you with quotes for the service that you require. 

We may use the information you provide to contact you, for product administration and for customer research. The information we capture may be used only by TheSnugg.com. Where we use your personal information to tell you about other products and services we will give you the opportunity to inform us that you do not wish your details to be used in this way. 

Except as described above we will not pass your personal information to third parties without your consent. 

Safeguarding your personally identifiable information We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. 

Review, correction and deletion of information from our files If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by us is not correct, or should you wish to have your personal information removed from our records, please contact us by email at enquiries@thesnugg.com and we will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. 

##  Payment

Your credit/debit card details will be encrypted by Thwate, a secure server, certified to accept credit card payments online to minimise the possibility of unauthorised access or disclosure, making your details safe and secure. 

All major credit/debit cards are accepted for payment, this is a secure website. Every time you enter an area of the site that has or requires sensitive information such as credit card details, an icon at the bottom of your browser window will appear which will resemble a closed padlock or an unbroken key. We use Internet standard SSL encryption technology to scramble your sensitive data when you transmit it to us. 

We do not store any payment information on our servers.
